Finding Aid for University of Michigan Class Albums
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 1873 Class Album (Literary)
  - Graduates
    - Haskell, Henry M. (Box 23)
    - Head, William J. (Box 23)
    - Hemingway, John M. (Box 23)
    - Jacobs, Albert P. (Box 23)
    - Keeler, Charles B. (Box 23)
    - Keenan, Walter M. (Box 23)
    - Keeney, Joseph R. (Box 23)
    - King, Charles Edward (Box 23)
    - Knappen, Loyal E. (Box 23)
    - Lewis, Joseph M. (Box 23)
    - Lockwood, Henry H. (Box 23)
    - McEldowney, John A. (Box 23)
    - Pattengill, Judson G. (Box 23)
    - Peabody, Sherwood R. (Box 23)
    - Perkins Joseph W. (Box 23)
    - Perley, Harry Otis (Box 23)
    - Peters, Herbert D. (Box 23)
    - Robison, George F. (Box 23)
    - Ross, Marshall Key (Box 23)
    - Russell, Henry (Box 23)
    - Rust, George (Box 23)
    - Scott, Zar Delavan (Box 23)
    - Sheeran, William Smith (Box 23)
    - Spalding, Volney M. (Box 23)
    - Stephens, Clarence M. (Box 23)
    - Stewart, Charles C. (Box 23)
    - Tappey, Ernest Taylor (Box 23)
    - Thayer, Edward E. (Box 23)
    - Todd, Albinus Levi (Box 23)
    - Tower, Cyrus O. (Box 23)
    - VanCleve, Charles M. (Box 23)
    - Voight, William (Box 23)
    - Walker, Franklin H. (Box 23)
    - Wells, Charles R. (Box 23)
    - White, John L. (Box 23)
    - Williams, William B. (Box 23)
    - Willis, Josiah Wyatt (Box 23)
    - Wilson, Charles L. (Box 23)
    - Wilson, Charles Scotts (Box 23)
    - Winchell, Charles M. (Box 23)
    - Wood, Edward W. (Box 23)
    - Woodruff, Eugene B. (Box 23)
    - Young, Kimball (Box 23)
    - Yule, James William (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs
    - Angell, James Burrill, Pres. Univ. of Michigan, 1871- (Box 23)
    - Adams, Charles Kendall, Member of Faculty 1862-1885 (Box 23)
    - Apollo Belvedere (Box 23)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 23)
    - Bennett, Henry D., Secretary of University 1869-1883 (Box 23)
      [13A]
    - Brochers, Albert A., Non-graduate of Literary Dept. (Box 23)
    - Campbell, James Valentine, Member of Faculty 1859-1885 (Box 23)
    - Campus (Box 23)
    - Campus [Long Walk] (Box 23)
    - Campus [Short Walk] (Box 23)
    - Christian Association Hall (Box 23)
    - Class of 1873 (Box 23)
      [113B]
    - Class of 1874 (Box 23)
    - Class of 1875 (Box 23)
    - Class of 1876 (Box 23)
    - Cocker, William J., President of the Univ. of Michigan, 1890- (Box 23)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre, Member of the Faculty, 1859- (Box 23)
  - Faculty and Miscellaneous Photographs
    - Denison, Charles Simeon, Member of Faculty, 1872- (Box 23)
    - DePont, Paul R., Member of Faculty 1871 (Box 23)
    - D'Ooge, Martin Luther, Member of Faculty 1867 (Box 23)
    - Doolittle, Charles L., Graduate of Literary Department, Class of 1874 (Box 23)
    - Douglas, Silas H., Member of Faculty 1844-1877 (Box 23)
    - Ford, Corydon La, Member of Faculty, 1854- (Box 23)
      [107B]
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons, Acting President, 1869-71, 1880-82 (Box 23)
    - Frothingham, George E., Member of Faculty 1867-1869 (Box 23)
    - General Library [Interior] (Box 23)
    - Harbison, Robert, Member of Faculty 1871-1873 (Box 23)
    - Haven, Erastus O., President of the University, 1863-69 (Box 23)
    - Hayman, Frank C., Graduate of the Univ. of Michigan, Class of 1874 (Box 23)
    - Hayman, Wayne, Graduate of Law Dept., Class of 1875 (Box 23)
    - Huron River (Box 23)
    - Huron Street (Box 23)
    - "Jimmie" (Box 23)
    - Kent, Charles Artemas, Member of Faculty 1868-1886 (Box 23)
    - Laboratory (Box 23)
    - Laocoön Group et al. (Box 23)
    - Law and Literary buildings (Box 23)
    - Law Building (Box 23)
    - Maclean, Donald, Member of Faculty, 1872-89 (Box 23)
    - Medical Building (Box 23)
      [107A]
    - Merriman, George Benjamin, Acting Professor, 1871-75 (Box 23)
    - Morris, George Sylvester, Member of Faculty 1870-1889 (Box 23)
    - Nydia and Ruth Gleaning (Box 23)
    - Observatory (Box 23)
    - Olney, Edward, Member of Faculty, 1863-87 (Box 23)
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin, Member of Faculty, 1852-87 (Box 23)
    - "Poultry Raising Association" of 1872 (Box 23)
    - Q C Society [Quadrantic Club] (Box 23)
    - "Robert" (Box 23)
    - Rose, Preston B., Member of Faculty, 1861-81 (Box 23)
    - Sager, Abram, Member of Faculty, 1842-75 (Box 23)
    - Spence, Adam Knight, Member of Faculty, 1858-70 (Box 23)
    - State Street, M. E. Church (Box 23)
    - Tappan, Henry Philip, President of the Univ. of Michigan, 1852-63 (Box 23)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit, Member of Faculty, 1867-81 (Box 23)
    - University Hall building (Box 23)
    - Walker, Charles Irish, Member of Faculty, 1859-76, 1879-81, 1886-87 (Box 23)
    - Walter, Edward L., Member of Faculty, 1868- (Box 23)
    - Watson, James Craig, Member of Faculty, 1858-79 (Box 23)
    - Williams, George P., Member of Faculty, 1863-81 (Box 23)
    - Wilson, Orrin S., Graduate of Literary Dept. 1874 (Box 23)
    - Winchell, Alexander, Member of Faculty, 1879- (Box 23)
    - Wood, DeVolson, 1857-72 (Box 23)
- 1873 Class Album (Henry E. Gelston)
  - Professors
    - Dr. Tappan (Box 24)
    - Dr. Haven (Box 24)
    - Dr. Angell (Box 24)
    - Prof. Williams (Box 24)
    - Dr. Douglass (Box 24)
    - Dr. Ford (Box 24)
    - Prof. Frieze (Box 24)
    - Prof. Watson (Box 24)
    - Prof. Olney (Box 24)
    - Prof. Adams (Box 24)
    - Prof. Tyler (Box 24)
    - Prof. Cocker (Box 24)
    - Dr. Prescott (Box 24)
    - Prof. D'Ooge (Box 24)
    - Prof. Morris (Box 24)
    - Prof. Merriman (Box 24)
    - Prof. Walter (Box 24)
    - Prof. Pattengill (Box 24)
    - Prof. Harrington (Box 24)
    - Prof. DePont (Box 24)
    - Prof. Harbison (Box 24)
    - Prof. Spence (Box 24)
    - Prof. Winchell (Box 24)
    - Prof. Wood (Box 24)
    - Prof. Jones (Box 24)
    - Dr. Sager (Box 24)
    - Dr. Palmer (Box 24)
    - Prof. Ten Brook (Box 24)
    - Judge Campbell (Box 24)
    - Prof. Walker (Box 24)
    - Judge Cooley (Box 24)
    - Prof. Kent (Box 24)
    - Mr. Bennett (Box 24)
  - Students
    - Benson, William (Box 24)
    - Bishop, Arthur G. (Box 24)
    - Bliss, Frank (Box 24)
    - Borchers, Albert A. (Box 24)
    - Brush, Eliot H. (Box 24)
    - Brush, Alfred E. (Box 24)
    - Buzzell, Wilbur (Box 24)
    - Burrit, Dwight N. (Box 24)
    - Carrier, William M. (Box 24)
    - Clarke, William F. (Box 24)
    - Cocker, Henry R. (Box 24)
    - Darling, John A. (Box 24)
    - Davis, Herbert E. (Box 24)
    - Decker, Wilhelmus (Box 24)
    - Doolittle, Charles L. (Box 24)
    - Douglas, Samuel T. (Box 24)
    - Dane, Charles H. (Box 24)
    - Eastman, Sidney C. (Box 24)
    - Emery, Thomas (Box 24)
    - Elliott, Henry W. (Box 24)
    - Fairbank, Henry W. (Box 24)
    - Farr, Frank W. (Box 24)
    - Ferdon, Edwin J. (Box 24)
    - Fox, William H. (Box 24)
    - Galloway, Elias D. (Box 24)
    - Gelston, Henry W. (Box 24)
    - Gass, Herschel R. (Box 24)
    - Gass, Marshall T. (Box 24)
    - Gleason, Clark H. (Box 24)
    - Goffe, James R. (Box 24)
    - Granger, William W. (Box 24)
    - Guernsey, Frank W. (Box 24)
    - Hapgood, Mary F. (Box 24)
    - Gross, Robert S. (Box 24)
    - Harrison, Richard D. (Box 24)
    - Haskell, Henry M. (Box 24)
    - Hayman, Wayne (Box 24)
    - Hayman, Frank (Box 24)
    - Head, William J. (Box 24)
    - Hemingway, John M. (Box 24)
    - Jacobs, Albert P. (Box 24)
    - Keeler, Charles B. (Box 24)
    - Kernan, Walter M. (Box 24)
    - Kerney, Joseph R. (Box 24)
    - King, Charles E. (Box 24)
    - Knappen, Loyal E. (Box 24)
    - Lewis, Joseph M. (Box 24)
    - Lockwood, Henry H. (Box 24)
    - McEldowney, John A. (Box 24)
    - Pattengill, Judson G. (Box 24)
    - Peabody, Sherwood R. (Box 24)
    - Perkins, Joseph W. (Box 24)
    - Perley, Harry O. (Box 24)
    - Peters, Herbert D. (Box 24)
    - Robinson, George (Box 24)
    - Ross, Marshall K. (Box 24)
    - Russel, Harry (Box 24)
    - Rust, George (Box 24)
    - Sheeran, William S. (Box 24)
    - Spalding, Volney M. (Box 24)
    - Stephens, Clarence M. (Box 24)
    - Stewart, Charles C. (Box 24)
    - Scott, Zar D. (Box 24)
    - Tappey, Ernest T. (Box 24)
    - Thayer, Edward E. (Box 24)
    - Todd, Albinus L. (Box 24)
    - Tower, Cyrus O. (Box 24)
    - VanCleve, Charles M. (Box 24)
    - Voight, William (Box 24)
    - Walker, Franklin H. (Box 24)
    - Wells, Charles R. (Box 24)
    - White, John L. (Box 24)
    - Williams, William B. (Box 24)
    - Willis, Joseph W. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Charles L. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Charles S. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Roin S. (Box 24)
    - Winchell, Charles M. (Box 24)
    - Wood, Edward W. (Box 24)
    - Woodruff, Eugene B. (Box 24)
    - Young, Kimball (Box 24)
    - Yule, James W. (Box 24)
    - Professors (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - "Robert" (Box 24)
    - "Jimmie" (Box 24)
    - Class of 1873 (Box 24)
    - Medical Laboratory, Law Building, Museum, Literary Building (Box 24)
    - Museum and Literary Building (Box 24)
    - Laboratory (Box 24)
    - Law Building (Box 24)
    - Medical Building (Box 24)
    - Walk to Laboratory and Medical Building (Box 24)
    - Walk to Museum and Literary Building (Box 24)
    - Union School, State Street, M. E. Church (Box 24)
    - Huron Street (Box 24)
    - Alpha Nu Hall (Box 24)
    - Chapel (Box 24)
    - Christian Association Hall (Box 24)
    - Apollo, Center of Museum (Box 24)
    - Library (Box 24)
    - Laocoon and his two sons (Box 24)
    - Apollo Belvedere (Box 24)
    - Ruth, Gleaning (Box 24)
    - Nydia (Box 24)
    - Observatory (Box 24)
      [137]
    - Union School (Box 24)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 24)
    - Cedar Bend, Ann Arbor (Box 24)
      [140]
- 1873 Class Album (C. C. Stewart)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - University Hall and Literary Building (Box 25)
    - View of Law Department and University Hall (Box 25)
    - Law Department (Box 25)
    - Chemical Laboratory (Box 25)
    - Law Department (Box 25)
    - View of Ann Arbor (Box 25)
    - Diagonal Walk (Box 25)
    - Walk to University Hall (Box 25)
    - M. E. Church (Box 25)
    - Unidentified street (Box 25)
    - Detroit Observatory (Box 25)
  - University Presidnets
    - Tappan, H. P. (Box 25)
    - Haven, E. O. (Box 25)
    - Angell, J. B. (Box 25)
  - Professors
    - Williams, George P. (Box 25)
    - Cocker, Benjamin F. (Box 25)
    - Douglas, Silas H. (Box 25)
    - Labeled "Prof. Wood?" but looks like Corydon La Ford (Box 25)
    - Frieze, Henry S. (Box 25)
    - Watson, G. C. (Box 25)
    - Olney, E. (Box 25)
    - Tyler, Moses C. (Box 25)
    - Wood, DeVolson (Box 25)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 25)
    - D'Ooge, Martin L. (Box 25)
    - Morris, George S. (Box 25)
    - Merriman, George B. (Box 25)
    - Walter, Edward L. (Box 25)
    - Pattengill, Albert H. (Box 25)
    - Unidentified man (Box 25)
  - Class Photos
    - Class of 1873 (Box 25)
    - Class of 1874 (Box 25)
    - Class of 1875 (Box 25)
    - Class of 1876 (Box 25)
  - Students
    - Benson, William (Box 25)
    - Bishop, Arthur G. (Box 25)
    - Borchers, Albert (Box 25)
    - Bliss, Frank (Box 25)
    - Buzzell, Wilber (Box 25)
    - Brush, Alfred E. (Box 25)
    - Brush, Eliot H. (Box 25)
    - Burritt, Dwight N. (Box 25)
    - Carrier, William M. (Box 25)
    - Clarke, William F. (Box 25)
    - Cocker, Henry R. (Box 25)
    - Darling, John H. (Box 25)
    - Davis, Herbert E. (Box 25)
    - Decker, William (Box 25)
    - Doolittle, Chas I. (Box 25)
    - Douglas, Samuel T. (Box 25)
    - Dane, Chas. H. (Box 25)
    - Eastman, Sidney C. (Box 25)
    - Emery, Thomas (Box 25)
    - Elliott, Henry W. (Box 25)
    - Fairbank, Henry W. (Box 25)
    - Farr, Frank W. (Box 25)
    - Ferdon, Edwin J. (Box 25)
    - Fox, William H. (Box 25)
    - Galloway, Elias D. (Box 25)
    - Gass, Hershall R. (Box 25)
    - Gass, Marshall T. (Box 25)
    - Gelston, Henry W. (Box 25)
    - Gleason, Clarke H. (Box 25)
    - Goffe, Jas R. (Box 25)
    - Granger, William W. (Box 25)
    - Gross, Robert S. (Box 25)
    - Guernsey, E. W. (Box 25)
    - Hapgood, Mary F. (Box 25)
    - Harrison, Richard D. (Box 25)
    - Haskel, Henry M. (Box 25)
    - Hayman, Wayne (Box 25)
    - Hemmingway, John Maynard (Box 25)
    - Head, William J. (Box 25)
    - Jacobs, Albert P. (Box 25)
    - Keeler, Chas B. (Box 25)
    - Keenan, Walter M. (Box 25)
    - Keeney, Joseph R. (Box 25)
    - King, Chas. E. (Box 25)
    - Knappen, Loyal E. (Box 25)
    - Lewis, Joseph M. (Box 25)
    - Lockwood, Henry M. (Box 25)
    - McEldowney, John L. (Box 25)
    - Pattengill, Judson G. (Box 25)
    - Peabody, Sherwood R. (Box 25)
    - Perkins, Joseph W. (Box 25)
    - Perley, Harry C. (Box 25)
    - Peters, Herbert D. (Box 25)
    - Robinson, George F. (Box 25)
    - Ross, Marshall K. (Box 25)
    - Russell, Henry (Box 25)
    - Rust, George (Box 25)
    - Sheeran, W.S. (Box 25)
    - Spalding, Volney M. (Box 25)
    - Stephens, Clarence M. (Box 25)
    - Stewart, Chas C. (Box 25)
    - Scott, Zar D. (Box 25)
    - Tappey, Ernest T. (Box 25)
    - Thayer, Edward E. (Box 25)
    - Todd, Albinus L. (Box 25)
    - Tower, Cyrus O. (Box 25)
    - VanCleve, Chas M. (Box 25)
    - Voigt, William (Box 25)
    - Walker, Frank H. (Box 25)
    - Wells, Chas R. (Box 25)
    - White, John L. (Box 25)
    - Williams, William B. (Box 25)
    - Willis, Josiah W. (Box 25)
    - Wilson, Chas Lyman (Box 25)
    - Wilson, Chas S. (Box 25)
    - Wilson, Orrin S. (Box 25)
    - Winchell, Chas M. (Box 25)
    - Wood, Edward W. (Box 25)
    - Woodruff, E.B. (Box 25)
    - Young, Kimball (Box 25)
    - Yule, James W. (Box 25)
    - Unidentified (Box 25)
- 1873 Class Album (J. G. Pattengill)
  - University Presidents
    - President Tappan (Box 26)
    - President Haven (Box 26)
    - President Angell (Box 26)
  - Students
    - Benson, William (Box 26)
    - Bishop, Arthur Giles (Box 26)
    - Bliss, Frank (Box 26)
    - Borchers (Box 26)
    - Brush, Alfred Erskine (Box 26)
    - Brush, Eliot Hunt (Box 26)
    - Buzzell, Wilbur (Box 26)
    - Burritt, Dwight Nathan (Box 26)
    - Carrier, William Henry (Box 26)
    - Clark, William Flint (Box 26)
    - Cocker, Henry Reed (Box 26)
    - Darling, John Henry (Box 26)
    - Davis, Herbert Erastus (Box 26)
    - Decker,Wilhelmus (Box 26)
    - Doolittle (Box 26)
    - Douglas, Samuel T. (Box 26)
    - Dane, Charles Henry (Box 26)
    - Eastman, Sidney C. (Box 26)
    - Emory, Thomas (Box 26)
    - Elliott, Henry William (Box 26)
    - Fairbank, Henry W. (Box 26)
    - Ferdon, Edwin Jacob (Box 26)
    - Fox, William Henry (Box 26)
    - Farr, Frank Ward (Box 26)
    - Galloway, Elias Durfee (Box 26)
    - Gelston, Henry Wisewell (Box 26)
    - Gass, Herschell Robert (Box 26)
    - Gass, Marshall Thomas (Box 26)
    - Gleason, Clark Hough (Box 26)
    - Gough, James Riddle (Box 26)
    - Granger, William W. (Box 26)
    - Gross, Robert Spear (Box 26)
    - Guernsey, Frank Ward (Box 26)
    - Hapgood, Mary Frances (Box 26)
    - Harrison, Richard D'Armond (Box 26)
    - Haskell, Henry Marsh (Box 26)
    - Hayman, Wayne (Box 26)
    - Hayman, Frank Clark (Box 26)
    - Head, William John (Box 26)
    - Hemingway, John Maynard (Box 26)
    - Jacobs, Albert Poole (Box 26)
    - Keeler, Charles Butler (Box 26)
    - Keenan, Walter Monroe (Box 26)
    - Keeney, Joseph R. (Box 26)
    - King, Charles Edward (Box 26)
    - Knappen, Loyal Edwin (Box 26)
    - Lewis, Joseph Marvin (Box 26)
    - Lockwood, Henry H. (Box 26)
    - McEldowney, John Alexander (Box 26)
    - Pattengill, Judson Gregory (Box 26)
    - Peabody, Sherwood Raymond (Box 26)
    - Perkins, Joseph Willilam (Box 26)
    - Perley, Harry Otis (Box 26)
    - Peters, Herbert Dwight (Box 26)
    - Robinson, George Francis (Box 26)
    - Ross, Marshall Key (Box 26)
    - Russell, Harry (Box 26)
    - Rust, George (Box 26)
    - Sheeran, William Smith (Box 26)
    - Spalding, Volney Morgan (Box 26)
    - Stephens, Clarence M. (Box 26)
    - Stewart, Charles C. (Box 26)
    - Scott, Zar Delavan (Box 26)
    - Tappey, Ernest Taylor (Box 26)
    - Thayer, Edward Ernest (Box 26)
    - Todd, Albinus Levi (Box 26)
    - Tower, Cyrus Obadiah (Box 26)
    - Van Cleve, Charles McKinstry (Box 26)
    - Voight, William (Box 26)
    - Walker, Franklin H. (Box 26)
    - Wells, Charles Russell (Box 26)
    - White, John L. (Box 26)
    - Williams, William Brown (Box 26)
    - Willis, Joseph Wyatt (Box 26)
    - Wilson, Charles Lyman (Box 26)
    - Wilson, Charles Scotto (Box 26)
    - Wilson, O. S. (Box 26)
    - Winchell, Charles McAllister (Box 26)
    - Woodruff, Eugene B. (Box 26)
    - Wood, EdwinWhite (Box 26)
    - Young, Kimball (Box 26)
    - Yule, James William (Box 26)
  - Professors
    - Professor Williams (Box 26)
    - Dr. Douglass (Box 26)
    - Dr. Ford (Box 26)
    - Professor Frieze (Box 26)
    - Professor Watson (Box 26)
    - Professor Olney (Box 26)
    - Professor Adams (Box 26)
    - Professor Tyler (Box 26)
    - Professor Cocker (Box 26)
    - Professor D'Ooge (Box 26)
    - Professor Morris (Box 26)
    - Dr. Prescott (Box 26)
    - Professor Greene (Box 26)
    - Assistant Professor Merriman (Box 26)
    - Asst. Professor Walter (Box 26)
    - Asst. Professor Pattengill (Box 26)
    - Asst. Professor Davis (Box 26)
    - Dr. Rose (Box 26)
    - Asst. Professor Harrington (Box 26)
    - Instructor DePont (Box 26)
    - Instructor Berman (Box 26)
    - Instructor Harbison (Box 26)
    - Instructor Blackburn (Box 26)
    - Instructor Dennison (Box 26)
    - Instructor Denman (Box 26)
    - Instructor Hutchins (Box 26)
    - Instructor Hennequin (Box 26)
    - Professor Spence (Box 26)
    - Professor Winchell (Box 26)
    - Professor Wood (Box 26)
    - Acting Professor Jones (Box 26)
    - Dr. Sager (Box 26)
    - Dr. Palmer (Box 26)
    - Librarian Ten Brook (Box 26)
    - Judge Campbell (Box 26)
    - Judge Walker (Box 26)
    - Judge Cooley (Box 26)
    - Professor Kent (Box 26)
  - Buildings and Miscellaneous
    - "Jimmy" (Box 26)
    - "Pluto" (Box 26)
    - "Robert" (Box 26)
    - Alpha Delta Phi (Box 26)
    - '73 Peninsular Chapter (Box 26)
    - Emblems (Box 26)
    - Campus--Autumn (Box 26)
    - University Hall (Box 26)
    - Law Department (Box 26)
    - Chemical Laboratory (Box 26)
    - Medical Department (Box 26)
    - Observatory (Box 26)
    - Diagonal Walk (Box 26)
    - Walk to University Hall (Box 26)
    - Laocoon Group et. al (Box 26)
    - Apollo Belvedere (Box 26)
    - Nydia (Box 26)
    - Ruth Gleaning (Box 26)
      [141]
    - General Library (Box 26)
    - Chapel (Box 26)
    - State Street (Box 26)
    - Huron Street (Box 26)
    - Cedar Bend (Box 26)
    - Ann Arbor from N. W. (Box 26)
    - Law Building (Box 26)
- 1874 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Adams, Charles Kendall (Box 27)
    - Angell, JamesBurrill (Box 27)
    - Bennett, Henry DeWitt (Box 27)
    - Campbell, James Valentine (Box 27)
    - Cocker, Benjamin Franklin (Box 27)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 27)
    - DePont, Paul Rousseau (Box 27)
    - D'Ooge, Rev. Martin Luther (Box 27)
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton (Box 27)
    - Dunster, Edward Swift (Box 27)
    - Ford, Corydon La (Box 27)
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 27)
    - Frothingham, George Edward (Box 27)
    - Gerrish, Frederick Henry (Box 27)
    - Greene, Charles Ezra (Box 27)
    - Harrington, Mark Walrod (Box 27)
    - Haven, Rev. Erastus Otis (Box 27)
    - Hennequin, Alfred (Box 27)
    - Hilgard, Eugene Woldemar (Box 27)
    - Hutchins, Harry Burns (Box 27)
    - Irving, Pierre Leslie (Box 27)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 27)
    - Kent, Charles Artemas (Box 27)
    - MacLean, Donald (Box 27)
    - Merriman, George Benjamin (Box 27)
    - Morris, George Sylvester (Box 27)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 27)
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin (Box 27)
    - Pattengill, Albert Henderson (Box 27)
    - Prescott, Albert Benjamin (Box 27)
    - Rose, Preston Benjamin (Box 27)
    - Sager, Abram (Box 27)
    - Tappan, Henry Philip (Box 27)
    - Ten Brook, Andrew (Box 27)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 27)
    - Walker, Charles Irish (Box 27)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine (Box 27)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 27)
    - Watson, James Craig (Box 27)
    - Williams, Rev. George Palmer (Box 27)
  - Members of the Class
    - Adams, Isaac (Box 27)
      [43.]
    - Arnold, Frances Eugene (Box 27)
    - Axtell, Frank Lawton (Box 27)
    - Babcock (?) (Box 27)
    - Barnard, Horace (Box 27)
    - Bean, Clarence Orrin (Box 27)
    - Benton, Eliza (Box 27)
    - Brennan, Michael (Box 27)
    - Brigham, Oshea Stowell (Box 27)
    - Buzzell, Delos (Box 27)
    - Cady, Frederick Augustus (Box 27)
    - Cady, Orrin (Box 27)
    - Carle, Frank Austin (Box 27)
    - Challis, DeWitt Clinton (Box 27)
    - Chandler, Anna Minerva (Box 27)
    - Clark, Alpheus Whitney (Box 27)
    - Come, Robert Harris (Box 27)
    - Cook, Charles (Box 27)
    - Ensign, John Edward (Box 27)
    - Everett, James Marcus (Box 27)
    - Follett, Lyman Decatur (Box 27)
    - Glenn, George Pinckney (Box 27)
    - Glover, James Henry (Box 27)
    - Granger, Annie (Box 27)
    - Gross, George Fiske (Box 27)
    - Hall, Edmund George (Box 27)
    - Hall, Emma Maria (Box 27)
    - Hall, John Townsend (Box 27)
    - Hamlin, Sarah Dix (Box 27)
    - Harding, George Lester (Box 27)
    - Hayman, Frank Clark (Box 27)
    - Hibbard, Charles Coe (Box 27)
    - Hinman, Edward Charles (Box 27)
    - Holmes, Horace (Box 27)
    - Hoyt, Almon Franklin (Box 27)
    - Hull, Julian Switzer (Box 27)
    - Jackson, Henry Bean (Box 27)
    - Jameson, George Hugh (Box 27)
    - Johnston, Theodore Hitchcock (Box 27)
    - King, Louis Buhl (Box 27)
    - Lane, Chester Taylor (Box 27)
    - Lane, Victor Hugo (Box 27)
    - Lungren, Charles Marshall (Box 27)
    - Matthews, Don Alonzo (Box 27)
    - Maxwell, Lawrence (Box 27)
    - May, Charles Henry (Box 27)
    - Maynard, Fred Augustus (Box 27)
    - Miller, Joseph Ronald (Box 27)
    - Parker, Henry St. Clair (Box 27)
    - Pattengill, Henry Romaine (Box 27)
    - Platt, Causten George (Box 27)
    - Potter, James Farwell (Box 27)
    - Reed, Wilbur Fisk (Box 27)
    - Richardson, John Sullivan (Box 27)
    - Rogers, Henry Wade (Box 27)
    - Rumsey, James Llewellyn (Box 27)
    - Sadler, Seymour McGlune (Box 27)
    - Sheldon, Mary Downing (Box 27)
    - Smith, Wilbert Wesley (Box 27)
    - Thayer, Herbert Artemas (Box 27)
    - Thomas, Calvin (Box 27)
    - Thomas, Charles Joseph (Box 27)
    - Thurber, Henry Thomas (Box 27)
    - Townsend, William Henry (Box 27)
    - Vorce, John VanBuren (Box 27)
    - Warner, James Dickinson (Box 27)
    - Warren, Charles Ashley (Box 27)
    - Wells, William Henry (Box 27)
    - West, Francis James (Box 27)
    - Wheatley, John Newton (Box 27)
    - Wheeler, Levi Lockwood (Box 27)
    - White, Laura Rogers (Box 27)
    - Whitmore, Jayne Adams (Box 27)
    - Williams, Robert Edward (Box 27)
    - Wines, Levi Douglas (Box 27)
    - Wing, Charles Royal (Box 27)
    - Withey, Edward William (Box 27)
    - Woodruff, James Ennis (Box 27)
  - Campus Personalities
    - "Jimmy" the postman (Box 27)
    - "Robert" the janitor (Box 27)
    - Campus Views and Buildings (Box 27)
    - Class Stone of 1862 (Box 27)
    - North West View of Campus (Box 27)
    - University Hall-Mason Hall, South wing (Box 27)
    - Medical Building (Box 27)
    - Law Building (Box 27)
    - Chemical Laboratory (Box 27)
    - Observatory (Box 27)
    - Library Interior (Box 27)
    - University Hall Chapel (Box 27)
    - Campus Walk Leading to Chemical Laboratory (Box 27)
    - Campus Walk in Front of Haven Hall to Mason Hall (Box 27)
    - Lydia (Box 27)
    - Ruth Gleaning (Box 27)
    - Laocoon (Box 27)
    - Apollo Belvedere (Box 27)
    - Apollo (Box 27)
    - Emblems (Box 27)
  - Student Groups
    - Student Group (Box 27)
    - Psi U (Box 27)
    - Psi Upsilon (Box 27)
    - Student Group (Box 27)
    - Student Group (Box 27)
    - Student Group (Box 27)